urlcover.com 2010-01-04

# Free URL Redirection Service by UrlCover.com

**Privacy Statement**

In an effort to protect our clients' and site visitors privacy and rights, Url Cover has established a Privacy Policy which explains what information we gather on visitors and what we do with information that we gather.

We advise all visitors and clients to read and understand our privacy policy, and to check it periodically for any updates or revisions. If you have any questions about the contents of our statement, please feel free to contact us by using our contact page.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Url Cover collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site.

**Privacy**

Users' privacy is very important to Url Cover. We are committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to Url Cover.

**The Information We Collect**

Url Cover may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. Url Cover may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Usersâ€™ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.

**How We Use Information**

Url Cover may use personally identifiable information collected through our web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Url Cover only. Url Cover may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Url Cover. At no time will Url Cover's database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists.

**Disclosure of Information**

Any information provided to Url Cover is solely used for internal purposes and will not be sold or distributed in any fashion to outside parties.

**Information Maintenance**

Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

**Questions**

If you have any questions regarding this policy please email us using our contact page.
